media-newswire.com 2018-01-23

# Media-Newswire.com - Press Release Distribution - PR Agency

**Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy covers only information that is collected through this Website, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site or when collected from other sites that may be linked to this one. 

Media Newswire collects information from our users at several different points on our Website: 

**Registration**  
In order to use some areas of this Website, a user must first complete a registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to provide a more personalized experience on our site and also to enable press release tracking to our customers. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Media Newswire uses session ID cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. 

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Website servers, we collect and analyze log files. Information collected includes anonymous data like IP addresses, browser types, referring pages, pages visited and time spent on our site. This information is used in aggregate to analyze and improve our websites. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Security**  
This Website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off. 

**Customer Service**  
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account and we reply via email or by using our support ticket system, in accordance with the user’s wishes. 

**Legal Proceedings**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Website. 

**Web Links**  
This Website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Media Newswire, are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We distinguish these 3rd party web sites by methods such as either opening them in a separate browser window or within a frame indicating the area within is not part of our site. In these instances the privacy policy of Media Newswire website will not apply. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that you visit. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website. 

**Your Consent / Contact Us**  
By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information as outlined in this privacy policy. If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us. 

**Cookies/Third Party Cookies**  
Please be aware that by using this website, any third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your user's browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on your website including but not limited to Google Adsense cookies. You can adjust these settings by going into your web browser and changing the cookies settings. In Internet Explorer this is under Tools, Internet Options, Privacy, Advanced and in Mozilla Firefox, it is located in Tools, Options, Privacy, Cookies. 

Added April 1, 2009 * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
